kalahariresorts.com 2019-06-15

# Legal

Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC, Kalahari Resorts LLC and Kalahari Management Co. LLC (collectively, "we", "us", "our") are committed to safeguarding the privacy of every individual who visits our Internet sites ("Websites"), specifically www.KalahariResorts.com. The following Privacy Policy outlines the information we will collect through the Websites and how that information will be used. This Policy will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want this information collected or further disseminated. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Websites. 

 **Information We Collect** : 

Personally identifiable information -  
The term 'personally identifiable information' refers to data you voluntarily provide while using the Websites that identifies you and/or the company on whose behalf you are accessing and using the Websites. Examples of personal information may include data in connection with our services, such as your name, e-mail address, phone number, company affiliation, physical address and/or certain other personal information. 

Personally identifiable information is never collected through the Websites in a non-obvious manner. 

Non-personally identifiable information -

The term 'non-personally identifiable information' refers to general information collected through technology regarding Websites visitors and users that relates specifically to the Websites. For instance, when visiting the Websites, your IP address may be collected. An IP address is often associated with the portal or service through which you enter the Internet. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. 

The Websites also use cookies. A cookie is a text file placed on your computer’s hard drive that identifies your computer so the site can remember information you have told us before or activities you have carried out on our site. The cookies can only contain data you told us about yourself. They cannot examine your computer or read data from it. Cookies cannot transmit a virus or do damage to your system. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. By clicking on the Help portion of your browser's menu bar, you can learn how to reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. 

Examples of non-personally identifiable information collected include traffic patterns, number of visits to certain pages, visits from other Internet sites or to third-party Internet sites linked to the Websites, use of particular services and interest in services, information or features of the Websites or other parties made available through or found at the Websites. 

The Websites also utilize Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Learn more about how you can manage what information Google collects [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

 **How Information is Used** : 

Personally identifiable information -  
Personally identifiable information may be used to assist with marketing programs designed to identify broad market groups for specific promotional opportunities. By providing personally identifiable information for this purpose you agree to be placed on marketing lists and may receive promotional notices from us or our affiliates, from time to time. 

We may also use your personally identifiable information for operational uses. Examples include using your information to complete transactions requested by you (such as your purchase of a product or service, including room reservations, through the Websites), to send you administrative communications either about your account with us, or to share your personal information with our telephone reservations center in order to allow our staff to respond more promptly to your questions or requests when you call. 

Your personally identifiable information may be shared with reputable third parties, but only for use in advertising campaign delivery or to provide more relevant advertising. Your personally identifiable information may be combined with additional information provided by you or augmented from other data sources. 

We will not sell or rent any personally identifiable information collected with any party not affiliated with us without your express written consent, except as provided below. 

Non-personally identifiable information -  
Non-personally identifiable information is used to make the Websites more helpful, interesting and useful to our visitors. 

Non-personally identifiable information may be used to provide anonymous statistical analysis of visitor traffic patterns, administer the Websites and servers, to allow for the auditing of our services by third parties and to improve our services.

**Permission for Use** :  
We may collect and use personally identifiable information that you submit at the Websites in any manner consistent with uses in this Privacy Policy or disclosed elsewhere on the Websites at the point you submit such personal information. 

 **Privacy Statement Exceptions** :  
Special circumstances -  
We may monitor and, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required, disclose personally identifiable information to protect the security, property, assets and/or rights of Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and Kalahari Resorts LLC from unauthorized use, or misuse, of the Websites or anything found at the Websites. 

We reserve the right to disclose personally identifiable information of the users of the Websites for any law enforcement purpose at the request of any law enforcement body or in response to subpoena or as otherwise required by court or administrative agency. 

Sale of assets -  
No part of this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC to transfer all or part of its businesses or assets, including the Websites to an affiliate or independent third party at any time, for any purpose, without any limitation whatsoever. We specifically reserve the right to transfer personally identifiable information collected from the Websites to the buyer of that portion of our business relating to that information. You may opt out of continued use of your information by any buyer of the Websites. 

 **Links Provided to Other Internet Sites** :  
The Internet sites owned and operated by Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC may contain links to other Internet sites. These third party Internet sites may not follow the same privacy practices of Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the actions of third parties, including without limitation, any Internet site owners whose Internet sites may be reached through any Internet site owned or operated by Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and Kalahari Resorts LLC. For this reason, we strongly encourage you to view the privacy policies of these other sites prior to submitting any personally identifiable information to them. 

 **User Consent to This Privacy Policy** :  
Use of the Websites signifies your consent, as well as the consent of the company for whom you use the Websites and whose information you submit (if any), to this on-line Privacy Policy, including the collection and use of information by Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC, as described in this policy, and also signifies agreement to the Terms of Use for the Websites. Continued access and use of the Websites without acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy relieves us from responsibility to the user. 

 **Withdrawing Consent** :  
If, after permitting use of your personally identifiable information, you later decide that you no longer want us to include your information in our marketing database or otherwise contact you or to use your information in the manner disclosed in this Privacy Policy or at the Websites, simply tell us by contacting us using the resources listed at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.

 **Privacy Statement Modifications** :  
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time; notice of changes will be published on this page. Changes will always be prospective, not retroactive. 

 **Contacting Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC** :  
If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC or your dealings with Kalahari Development LLC, LMN Development LLC and/or Kalahari Resorts LLC, please [email](mailto:webmaster@kalahariresort.com) us or write us at: 

Internet Marketing  
Kalahari Waterpark Resort Convention Center  
P. O. Box 590  
Wisconsin Dells WI 53965  
10/19/2017
